One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Gold Roger, the legendary King of the Pirates, obtained everything the world has to offer.
What he said in his final moments drove countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure? Go ahead. Find it!
Everything is right where I left it!
Pirates have set out in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly entered... the Great Pirate Era!
Gotta keep movin’, just can't stop
Rarin’ for the dawn to arrive
One, two, sunshine, four, we go!
Hoist the flag for the break of romance dawn
Jump-start your day, ready to make waves
Reachin’ for fantastic realms
Need to put your toughness on display
Is bein’ brazen such a crime?
If you’re wanted, you’re a winner
Ah, freedom is our only rule
Worries don’t bother us at all
Keep on goin’, that's our pledge
Since the day our dreams began
Our aims remain the same
Sunlight won’t fade from our hearts
The sun of my heart will never set
One, two, sunshine... One, two, sunshine
One, two, sunshine, four, we go!
We go!
To the Deep Sea
Sabaody Archipelago
Brother, it's hard to dig!
Of course it is!
The island is made mostly out of tree roots.
Please forgive us, don't bury us!
I'll do anything, just don't kill me!
Captain Black forced us to do it!
Once we joined them, we thought...
we could kill the Straw Hats...
with high bounties...
easily from within, as we like!
Drip!
Hey, stop! He's gonna die!
Are you a devil fruit eater?!
D-Don't do it!
Yes! I got him...
Huh? What's going on here? A logia?!
But, look what happened!
I thought he just looked different
because I hadn't seen him for two years.
The pirate Straw Hat...
No wonder!
He was just a fake.
Do you think the gods
will forgive them, Coribou?
I dig! I dig!
That's right!
Let's bury them!
Oh gods!
Let us bury these fools!
Don't! Please don't kill us!
But I saw the real Straw Hat Luffy for myself!
Fake Straw Hats Gathering Point
I told you that I had no choice!
Dark King Rayleigh stood in our way!
He could even fight Uncle Kizaru equally!
What would you expect us to do?
The Caribou brothers and their crew
and some of the fake Straw Hats...
got away successfully.
We caught all the others but two pacifista
were severely damaged by the real Straw Hats.
One of them was the prototype
that cornered the Straw Hats two years ago.
Of course, his strength hasn't changed.
So they must have gotten stronger!
They've improved themselves
in last two years, big time!
Make sure to tell
Marine Headquarters in the New World.
The Straw Hats are completely revived!
They're gone before you know it.
Our little Monkey and everybody,
they all got stronger.
Were you watching?
Yes, I'm a fan of theirs.
You're thinking about something,
aren't you, Ray?
Well...
Yeah...
Hey, that's a nice ship!
I stole it.
My house burned down so I'm living here.
Yeah? And what's your name?
Rayleigh.
I'm Roger!
I think we were destined to meet, Rayleigh!
Destined?
Do you wanna turn the world
upside down with me?
Huh?
The world?
Who are you and where you from?
Go away!
Maybe nothing in this world
happens by accident.
As everything happens for a reason...
our destiny slowly takes form.
At any rate, Luffy looks great in that hat,
better than ever.
Maybe I want to live a little longer.
Beneath the Seas of the Sabaody Archipelago
The surface is far up there already.
What a view!
Submarines can't have windows this wide!
We're sinking and sinking!
I can't stop worrying about flooding!
Feels like we're leaving the inhabited
world. It makes me nervous!
C-C-Can we go back
on the surface again for sure?
I-It's not like I'm scared but...
It's beautiful down here!
Look at that!
Trees... No, roots!
Oh yeah!
Come to think of it, Sabaody Archipelago
consists of giant mangroves!
I'm overwhelmed by the beauty of nature!
I'm so surprised that my eyes could pop out!
Oh, but I don't have eyes.
I've seen this already.
Yeah, because you got on the wrong ship!
Shut up! Everybody's having a great time!
I can't believe these roots
are running down to the sea bottom!
They're enormous and magnificent!
I can't hold it any longer!
Hey, Chopper...
There's something behind that tree!
What?
Wow, it's huge!
How exciting!
An underwater adventure!
It's like a dream come true!
Oh, fish!
I think I can catch them!
The fish here look delicious too.
Stop it, you fools!
What if the bubble pops!
Don't ever do that again or I kill you!
Nami, give us some dos and don'ts on
the coated ship before they do something stupid.
Okay, Sanji!
Rayleigh gave me a note.
Alright, everyone, listen...
She's moving!
A real, beautiful woman!
– Sanji!
It's gonna pop! It's gonna pop!
How can you fly that far with nosebleed!
– What?!
– Sanji flew out into the water!
It's amazing.
The bubble doesn't break even under
tremendous pressure in this deep water
but things can pass through it like that.
Sanji!
Come back!
I feel weak in the water...
– Hang in there!
What happened to you, Sanji?!
You've become even more
susceptible to women!
This isn't like you!
I feel sorry for him...
What happened to Sanji the ladies' man
in the past two years?
At this rate, he's gonna bleed to death once
he meets the mermaids that he's longing to see.
I can't help worrying.
We'll have to call for blood
donations at Fishman Island.
I wonder if fishmen and mermaids
have the same blood as humans.
The bubble that coats the Sunny
has the same quality...
as the bubbles we just saw
at Sabaody Archipelago.
Stop analyzing the bubble
in such a calm manner!
Yes, Robin's right.
Basically, they're the same.
It stretches to a certain point and
beyond that, it allows things to get through.
Which means if we fire a gun or a cannon
at a creature that attacks us,
the bubble won't break.
Huh?
Then, on what occasion will it break instead?
As you can imagine, when there are
too many holes at once, it'll break.
For example, if we are bitten
by a sea king's fangs, it'll be trouble.
– It's coming from behind!
They're fighting... We're safe!
Or if the ship itself breaks up
by crashing into a rock or a trench,
the broken mast or planking will break
the bubble and that also spells danger.
So we have to be careful
with creatures and obstacles in the sea.
As long as we don't do anything
foolish from inside, it'll be fine.
I see! It's tougher than I thought!
But...
of the ships that head
for Fishman Island, 70% of them...
end up sinking. So be cautious.
– What's gonna happen?!
With my Gatling, I can catch
a whole school of fish!
Then let's see which of us can catch more fish!
Weren't you guys listening
to what Nami said?!
"Too many holes" is no good!
Don't ever try it again or I'll kill you!
Damn!
Hachi said he'd show us the way to Fishman Island
so I thought it was gonna be a safe trip!
Oh yeah!
They gave me a lot of lunches!
Since Sanji is sick, let's eat these, everybody!
I'm so starved!
My bones are starved!
Nami, the ship is gonna be stable for a while?
Don't we have to do anything?
Nope.
We just have to ride
this big sea current for now.
So, yeah, we can continue on
like this for a while.
We don't have much to do until later.
Then we have a little time, huh?
There's something that
I have to tell you all about.
– The robot's secrets?!
You have more secrets?!
What can you transform into?!
Or you have a secret weapon?!
Tell us, robot brother!
Super Armored Me!
Armored Me!
No, I'm afraid...
I'm afraid it's not about that-robo.
– Wow, cool! He speaks Robotese!
This is what I wanna tell you about.
Go ahead and eat while you're listening.
Hachi told us that he would show us
the way to Fishman Island,
but he got severely injured at Sabaody
and he's under medical care at Fishman Island.
He got injured for the same reason as Duval.
He had been protecting the Thousand Sunny.
Around a year ago, the Marines found out about
the Sunny and those two both faced fierce battles
and were taken out of commission.
Huh?
Then how did the ship
remain undamaged after that?
There was someone else who fought for it.
There was someone else?
He's the one who separated us two years ago.
The big Warlord: Bartholomew Kuma!
I couldn't believe my eyes
when I got to the Sunny a few days ago...
I've been expecting you.
What are you doing here?!
Mission accomplished.
There isn't even a scratch on the Sunny.
And Rayleigh told me later...
I work for the Revolutionary Army.
Since I have a connection with them,
I wanna let them get away from here.
I think you guys half expected that.
He saved our lives!
And after we vanished from the island,
Kuma visited Rayleigh and told him...
I...
don't have much time left.
I don't know what made him obey the Marines,
but he agreed to be a guinea pig and let his body
be modified into a cyborg piece by piece
and he somehow lost his personality
before the Summit War.
But I don't think he could guess what
each of us would do after we get separated!
Even so he waited for us
at the ship without his personality?
He made Dr. Vegapunk, who modified him...
agree to program a mission into his mind.
"Defend the pirate ship until the day that
one of the Straw Hats comes back to the ship."
That's why, for the past two years,
without his own memory,
he had been carrying out his own orders,
as a human weapon, waiting for us.
That's insane.
Why did he do such a thing for us?
Terms like "connection," "Revolutionary Army,"
remind me about Luffy's father,
the leader of the Revolutionary Army.
I don't know my father that well,
but that bear-like guy was a good guy, huh?
Kuma...
There is no mistake that he's the one
who gave us the past two worthwhile years.
We can't even ask him
why he did it but just remember that.
Bartholomew Kuma turned out
to be one of our greatest allies.
But even if we meet him again,
Kuma is now a heartless human weapon.
That's all I have to say.
I'm grateful, but I still have a lot of questions.
I hope we can find out his motive one day.
"Ally"?
Oh, you woke up, Sanji.
Eat lunch! It's from the Isle of Women!
Isle of Women?
Is that Kuma guy really an ally?
Don't you realize where I was
for the past two years?
What kind of training were you doing
at the dream island full of women, Luffy?
Now, now, Sanji.
I don't know what you've been through, but let's enjoy the voyage now!
Do you wanna sing with me?
Stop trying to cheer me up! I feel pathetic!
Brother, there he is. Straw Hat.
I can see that, you fool!
I'm gonna join them this time for sure!
How deeply are we submerged now?
It's getting darker and darker.
We went through the euphotic zone
and we're at the bottom of the twilight zone.
It must be more than
a thousand meters below.
It's really quiet.
It feels different from submersibles.
It feels like flying in the sky.
Whale! There is a whale!
Laboon! Laboon!
No, that's old man Whitebeard!
There's something
at six o'clock! Is it a creature?
No...
Are you guys all ready?!
Yes, brother!
– Yes, yes!
The target is right there!
It's easier to just destroy their ship
and let it be swallowed by the sea
but that's no good because
they won't know who did it to them.
We gotta cut their heads off and bring them back
to show the world what Caribou is capable of!
– Yes!
They're not ready to fight!
It's a complete surprise attack!
Don't make a mistake, guys!
– Yes!
Yes! Yes!
Hey, guys! There is a ship
kind of thing coming from behind!
What?
A ship?
It's coming towards us!
Charge!
It's a pirate ship!
They're pushing against us!
Go away! The bubble is gonna pop!
No! They're gonna come through the bubble!
Who are they?
Run!
Hard to port!
Go, sea cow!
They're coming after us!
That noise–
They're so persistent!
What do they want from us?
Stop!
The bubble is gonna pop!
You're doing great, sea cow!
– Yes!
Are they gonna come aboard?
Sea cow?
Wait a minute! That's...
The bubbles are joined!
Brother, now is the chance!
Alright!
Should we do it?!
– Yes!
Hey, Momoo!
Aren't you Momoo of the Arlong Pirates?
Do you remember me?
I'm Nami!
I was there at the Arlong Park!
Hey, Luffy...
Doesn't he look familiar?
Yeah?
Die, damn you!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Let's board their ship!
– Yes!
Whoa! He's coming through the bubble!
No, somebody's coming!
We gotta fight!
Guys!
Are you ready?!
– Yes!
While they're dumbfounded,
kill them all!
Let's go!
Yes!
Guys, follow my lead!
– What?!
What's the matter, sea cow?
Why, sea cow?
Oh no, we left Captain Caribou on that ship!
Brother!
Alright, by way of greeting,
fire the gatling gun!
Kill all the Straw Hats and...
Huh?
No! Don't throw me out into the water!
That's something you shouldn't do!
You have to value people's life!
The gods... The gods are watching
over you! Don't you think so?!
You're being inconsistent!
Weren't you gonna fire
a gatling gun and kill us all?!
No, that was just...
That was just a play on words.
That wasn't playing.
Who are you?
You must be the captain of the ship.
Oh, Roronoa Zoro!
No way! I'm not a captain!
I'm just...
I was forced to be a slave for them!
Oh, I'm sick of being on that ship!
Oh yeah! This is great!
Can I stay on this ship for a little while?
Please?
Well, he is kind of pathetic...
No way! He just made it up!
What?! He just made it up?!
Hey, where did you find the sea cow
who was drawing your ship?
Oh...
Here is...
one fine cutie!
You're the cat burglar.
Stop looking at our navigator like that!
Nami!
You're safe... now!
That's getting to be a pain!
I just caught that sea monster somewhere...
Experienced people
have those animals pull their ship.
What?!
Is that so?
Stop! Stop, sea cow!
What happened?
Brother! I'll save you!
I wanna find a sea monster.
Hey, Luffy!
What are you up to?
Let's start his rehabilitation
with some less stimulating pics.
Hey, Nami.
We're not exactly heading
where the log pose is pointing.
Yeah, that's fine.
The right course should be
southwest of where it's pointing.
It's faster to go straight.
Why should we do that?
If you go straight, you'd be
taken away by the sea current
and get stuck by a volcano
or an undersea mountain.
What?! Volcano!
It's scary to be in the water!
But I thought the sea currents
in the Grand Line were volatile.
Is there any stable current?
Yes, just one.
This is good.
Stay calm.
Everyone! It's gonna get colder from
here on out so wear a coat or something.
Yes, it's getting chilly. I can feel it on my skin.
Oh, but I don't...
You're a skeleton so you don't have skin.
Chopper...
You can't do that...
You can't steal my line...
Are we going somewhere cold?
Not the deep sea?
Don't you know that the water
in the deep sea is cold?
Like in a bathtub, hot water goes up
and cold water goes down.
Oh yeah? I'm not a big fan
of baths so I wouldn't know.
I see.
If the sea is the same as a bathtub,
it's gonna get colder as you go deeper.
The temperature isn't the only difference.
You're still depressed?!
In the deep layer of the sea...
Deep Current
Surface
Current
Present
Location
there are giant currents called deep currents
that you don't get to see very often.
Deep Current
Present
Location Surface
Current
Surface
Deep Current
Present
Location Surface
Current
Those currents flow totally
independently from surface currents.
Surface
Current
Present
Location
There are currents under currents?!
You know a lot!
Because I'm really old!
All currents are connected.
One current flows eastward
and the other one flows westward.
They could also flow upward or downward.
It's like a giant dragon.
Deep currents flow really slowly.
Once they flow to the deep sea,
it takes two thousand years...
until they flow upward to the surface.
Two thousand years?!
Yes...
That's why there are a number of myths
about the dark and undiscovered deep currents.
Monsters!
Curses!
Spirits of the dead!
What?!
There are ghosts in the deep sea?!
Huh? Really? I'm scared!
It's exciting!
Ghosts...
I don't know about that.
But we're gonna get on a downward flow.
That's how we get to the deep sea.
– So there's mystery currents...
You guys didn't understand a bit, did you?!
You wanna sing, Nami?
Shut up!
This is it!
Nami, I see it!
Yeah?
The mystery current?!
Where is it? Where is it?!
That's cool!
What is that?
So that's the downward current!
The Downwelling Current Plume!
How... cool!
It's like a massive...
waterfall in the sea!
The sea is "falling" far below!
At an extraordinary speed!
Interesting!
Nature's great!
What a spectacular stream!
I wonder how deep it is.
It's far greater than I had heard.
I can't see the bottom!
It's completely dark!
We're dead!
With that speed, we're gonna be
slammed into the bottom and die!
Is it really okay to go with the flow?
Don't worry about the ship.
Sunny is the strongest ship
built from Adam, the Jewel Tree.
No way!
I didn't know that it lives here...!
It's a demon that rules the realm of water!
And the enemy of the human race!
Straw Hats!
You should turn back now!
It's dangerous!
I had forgotten about you.
There is a monster!
It's...
It's right there...
Cut it out, guys!
B-Behind you...
What are you saying...
Is it...
behind me?
It's the kraken!
How huge! The monster octopus!
Looks like he broke a lot of ships!
Ships that had left for
the New World have been attacked!
Please! I don't wanna die!
Go back!
If you just wait for a few days, it would–
Shut up!
I have a good idea!
Let's tame him!
– Huh?